One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
No one will come to save you.
No one can escape from this bird cage.
Hello? Hello?
Communication with those outside of this island is also impossible.
You will all die, without anyone outside ever realizing a thing.
Your crazed neighbors will continue to...
mercilessly attack everyone.
Someone stop me!
Please, not the children!
Be they your family, your friends,
or even the citizens you strive to protect.
Stop it!
My body's moving on its own.
Someone stop me!
Everyone, get away from me!
Isshou-san...
You can run and you can hide,
but there isn't a single safe haven inside this cage.
Executive Officer Pica
The bird cage's terror will continue for days on end.
Will everyone die first?
Or will you all end this game first?
That bastard Doflamingo,
what the hell's he trying to start?!
What's going on?!
The factory rose up and disappeared somewhere!
But this is our chance!
We can get outside!
The day we can escape this
underground hell has come!
Thank you, God Usopp!
Let's go!
Robin-dono!
Kin'emon!
A-A steel breast-band.
Must be a foreign custom.
I like it.
R-Robin-senpai, make me your servant...
No, I misspoke.
There's something I want to ask you.
T-That man's nose...
It's exactly the same as that of the man who shot the flag on the Tower of Justice, Sogeking-senpai.
That's him. His name is Usopp.
It's him!
Robin-senpai was moved by the actions of this crew,
who made enemies of the world for the sake of one of their crewmates.
Together, they're the star duo of Enies Lobby!
Yes, yeah, yes!
What are you getting all excited about, you psycho? Shut up already!
Someone like that broke my arm...
I hand them over to you.
Though they may be small, they are great warriors.
Thank you, Topknotland.
They were unconscious in the palace corridors.
They put their lives on the line for the captain.
Kabu-san, Rampo, you did a great job.
Someone stop me! My body won't listen to me!
This is just like that night ten years ago.
I finally understand.
King Riku and the royal army were being controlled...
by Doflamingo!
Scream, hate, suffer.
You are all innocent victims.
Help...
Stop it, Doflamingo!
Think about it.
Will you come kill me?
Or fight alongside me to bring judgment upon the twelve fools who stand against me?
If you choose incorrectly, the game won't end.
For each star you get 100 million.
100 million belly?!
They are the outlaws of Dressrosa!
Pirate
Straw Hat Crew
"Cyborg Franky"
Dressrosa
Former Army Commander
Kyros
Pirate
Straw Hat Crew
"Pirate Hunter Zoro"
Revolutionary Army
Chief of Staff
Sabo
Dressrosa Former King
Riku Dold the Third
Pirate
Straw Hat Crew
Captain "Straw Hat Luffy"
Heart Pirates Captain
Seven Warlords of the Sea (Interim)
"The Surgeon of Death" Trafalgar Law
Corrida Colosseum
Prisoner Gladiator (Granddaughter of King Riku)
Rebecca Samurai from the Wano Kingdom
"Foxfire Kin'emon"
Dressrosa
Former Princess
Viola
Pirate
Straw Hat Crew
"The Devil's Child" Nico Robin
C-Commander Kyros!
I'd forgotten about him.
The invincible gladiator.
There are some pirates there as well.
The Straw Hat Pirates.
The Family commander Violet... was Princess Viola?!
And the main offenders of each organization...
are all three-stars!
300 million!
Law and Straw Hat.
That's the alliance that just shook the world.
K-King Riku?
King Riku, you're alive!
There's one of the revolutionary army's top guns too!
He's the chief of staff.
Information spreads fast.
Me too?!
T-Thank god he didn't find out about me.
Furthermore, there's the man who has angered me the most today.
He's the one who forced you all into this cruel game.
The one who kills him...
gets 500 million!
Pirate
Straw Hat Crew
"God"
Usopp
500 million!
We can live the rest of our lives in luxury!
F...
T-This is bad, Usoland's...
Five stars!
There are some one-stars and a three-star guy there as well.
Sabo-kun, what should we do?
We're escaping above ground.
Everyone, hurry!
God Usopp! Sorry, but please die!
Five stars is 500 million!
T-Those guys were worshiping me a minute ago!
Dammit, run away.
Understood.
There's one over there.
It's the one-star samurai.
A hundred million belly!
How troublesome.
A-According to the dwarves, this is the scrapyard.
Are you really down here, Kanjuurou?
The 100 million is mine!
To hell with it!
He fell!
The samurai fell into the hole!
You don't have time to hesitate.
Time is ticking,
people are dying, and the town is burning.
What should we do?
We've only just realized that King Riku was innocent...
If all of us were to go up against him, then maybe we could kill Doflamingo.
He's not alone though.
To defeat Doflamingo, we'd have to go through two thousand members of the Donquixote Family.
Then what are we supposed to do?
King Riku is among those twelve.
We shouldn't have to kill them.
Restraining them will do. There's only twelve of them.
We have no choice.
We have to fight.
Where'd Cyborg Franky disappear to?
Barrier!
Don't follow us.
Keep going toward the surface!
Zoro?
Yeah.
Where are you?
Is that Robin?
I'm with Luffy and the others right now.
It's called the "Royal Grounds".
We've been put in a really aggravating situation.
Robin? Did you see that?
Mingo's really annoying.
But Usopp's bit was hilarious.
What the hell, Luffy!
Rebecca was on that list as well, do you think she's okay?
Rebecca's...
I'm right here, Lucy.
Oh, perfect timing.
The soldier's right here...
Where'd the soldier go?
Don't tell me, he...
It's an outlaw, kill him!
Did Soldier-san...
Did Soldier-san turn back into a human?
Lucy, what kind of person is he?
What kind of person?
What are you talking about?
That one-legged soldier is...
your dad!
He's the guy from the statue in the Colosseum!
I-I couldn't protect her.
I knew it...
Soldier-san is valiant...
... and he will always watch over you.
I'm happy for you.
The soldier guy went somewhere, but listen, Rebecca.
Don't cry yet.
I won't let the soldier die.
Make sure you stay safe.
Sorry I couldn't give you the Flame Fruit that you wanted to eat.
But in exchange, I'll beat the crap out of Doflamingo!
So stay with my crewmates.
I'll end this game right away.
Stay alive!
You got it?!
Yeah!
Luffy, tell me who's there on your end.
Here we have...
Do you understand, Straw Hatter?
Our plan was to destroy the Smile factory to make Doflamingo and Kaidou clash.
If you take out Doflamingo now, Kaidou's rage at losing the Smiles will be directed at us.
It'll mean we have to fight an enraged Emperor!
We can worry about that later.
Just look at this country! I've gotta do something!
Find the outlaws!
If we want to survive, we have to catch them!
If you find any outlaws, let everyone know right away!
Somebody, please stop me!
That was close. Don't let your guard down.
Get moving.
Isshou-san, you're not going to capture Doflamingo?
We have to restrain as many of the people running rampant as possible.
Besides, our target here is the alliance between Straw Hat and Law.
Contact all our squadrons.
Wait, I'm still in handcuffs.
They'll come off soon enough.
As if!
I'll get the key.
I promise I'll find it, and-
What route are we taking?
Straight ahead!
He's not planning to jump, is he?!
Just you wait, Doflamingo!
Droves of people are pouring out from under the Colosseum!
It looks like all the upheaval caused the underground and the surface to merge!
These must be the people who were forced to work in that underground port!
Soldiers...
Officials...
Pirates!
I... I can't believe so many people were enslaved without anyone knowing!
Maynard, who told you to infiltrate the battle tournament?
Don't go off on your own like that.
You're lucky you're still alive.
But Bastille-san,
doing so let me see the whole picture of the tournament.
If we apprehend Doflamingo,
Navy HQ Vice-Admiral
Maynard the Pursuer (Participant in the tournament)
the balance of the world could shift!
Underground
Trading Port
This is...
a trading vessel from the Kingdom of Biggschots, disguised as a pirate ship.
The shadows from several countries have come together in this port.
Please, stop!
I-I'm so sorry!
Darling!
Everybody, run!
Why, Isshou-san?!
Doflamingo can't be allowed to be a Warlord any longer!
We should capture him right now!
I'm sure the Navy has been doing the same thing all along.
You've been in this organization a long time, right, Vice-Admiral?
Have you always ignored...
these enraged screams?
They're not crying. They're furious!
Do you think the World Government...
are gods?!
You will obey my decision.
Law and the others are after the Smiles, right?
Hey, Doffy, shouldn't we protect the factory?
The Land Where The Royal Palace Is (The Sunflower Field)
They'll never get in anyway. It's made of Sea Stone.
And I've got the keys right here.
Young master?!
Are you sure?!
Why give the enemy hope?
How weak you are.
You couldn't even protect one little girl,
Trebol.
Shut up, old G-zer! She's not really a little girl, you know!
Hey, hey, Doffy!
I'm really sorry about Sugar.
How could I have known that a man with both arms and legs tied could make her faint?
It was inconceivable!
It's the same with the Flame Fruit.
I had no idea that the Revolutionary Army's second-in-command was fighting in the tournament.
It was inconceivable!
No excuses, you disgraceful fools!
G, for disGraceful!
It's in the past.
Blaming you won't change anything.
Right? Our boss is the best!
Take that, Lao G!
If you insist, I will accept your forgiveness.
But Doffy, now the Navy will give us trouble.
What should we do about Fujitora?
I've settled matters with him. The Navy won't go after us.
But once Fujitora's use runs out,
we'll have to get rid of him.
To completely eliminate the system of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Nothing good will come from letting him live.
Though, getting rid of him won't be easy.
The Navy and the pirates...
You could just let me go all out...
That voice!
It's so...
... and I could wipe them all out on my own!
Donquixote Family Top Commander
Pica♠
His voice is so high!
How can that voice be coming out of that body?
I can't... I just can't get used to that voice!
But if I so much as giggle, I'm dead!
There's no need to rush.
Now listen. This game is something of a royal election.
I have asked the populace if the Rikus or the Donquixotes are more fit to rule the country.
The citizens will choose their king.
They have that right.
We simply crush the ones who come for us, and enjoy watching the rest kill each other.
But that'll take forever!
Doffy, I-
I-I'm so sorry, Pica-sama!
Please forgive him. He's new!
He just wasn't expecting you to sound so...
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
You're getting buried alive in stone!
Wait, Pica-sama!
Gatling Girl!
If you kill him, there won't even be a corpse left!
His family wouldn't appreciate that.
I'm sorry, Baby 5.
My mother died when I was eight.
I killed my father when I was ten.
My commanders are my family, who've been with me through thick and thin for many years.
They're the only ones I have.
I will never allow anyone to laugh at my family.
Do you understand?
Y-Yes, Sir!
Restrain everyone you find running wild!
Find the Straw Hats and Trafalgar Law!
Yes, Sir!
It looks like the Navy has no intention of fighting us -in.
So they still insist on treating the young master like a Warlord.
Doesn't that seem a bit too thoughtful?
They must be scared of the bird cage too!
Anyway, I can't believe that pervert had the strength to run away.
Where did he go?
That's gotta be the Smile factory.
It's sticking out like a sore thumb.
It's like it wants to get hit by my beam!
A balloon's falling down -in.
A balloon?
Law!
You've got some nerve showing your face here, you little brat!
Big Bro Law? I'd almost forgotten you existed.
Straw Hat Luffy!
Trafalgar Law!
The Pirate Hunter!
This is one hell of a place to land!
Straw Hat!
Once I'm free, I'm killing you first!
We'd be in trouble no matter where we landed.
This entire country is our enemy.
Anyway, let's run!
Yeah!
After them!
Zoro, not that way!
This isn't the right way either, Straw Hat!
Outlaws!
There are two three-stars and a two-star!
He got me! This weird guy just swam in the ground!
Now, Vise!
Run! He's a super-weight man!
Dammit! Let go of my legs!
Ton-Ton! Ten-Ton Vise!
I can't get free! My legs are stuck!
I won't miss this time!
Pistol High-Heel!
Heavy!
Ow!
Alright! My feet are free!
Keep it together! Now let's move!
We'll be taking your combined bounty of eight hundred million!
Prepare yourselves!
Fire!
Three-stars and a two-star!
This is such a pain!
Should we really cut them down?
There are civilians in there!
Alright, I'll use my Haki to...
Cease this.
No matter how many weak bullets you fire, you won't hit them.
A Navy Admiral...
The old gambler!
Usopp, the five-star, is in the Colosseum!
There he is! After him!
Get him!
Just leave me alone already!
With this altered geography, the Colosseum wall is pushed up against the royal grounds.
We can climb up there to meet with the others.
I found them!
Rebecca, go on ahead.
Robin-san!
You're mine!
Bartolomeo!
I'm so honored to have you address me by name, Robin-senpai!
I-I'll stop the enemies here.
Go on ahead with Sogeking-senpai.
Thank you.
Robin-senpai thanked me!
Now I'm really fired up!
I ain't letting anyone chase you any further!
What is he planning to do now?
I-It's happening again!
I-It can't be...
That's...
He's finally...
Once that guy shows up, it's all over!
Nobody can fight him!
What the hell is that?!
A giant...
He's way too big!
That's...
Pica!
Pica-sama!
Now, everyone who dares to oppose our family...
I will take you on!
That voice! It's so high!
Oh, come on!
It doesn't fit him at all!
What a weird voice!
Straw Hat!
Translation & initial timing, Yibis
Timing, Halee
Quality-checking, Simon, Galaxy 9000, Halee
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Simon, Galaxy 9000
Raw provider, GS-Raws